Oh, he's already taking
after Uncle Shelly.
(Amy:)-Come on, Sheldon, you should go.
-Why?
(Amy:)Well, you always
complain that you never
(Amy:)had an intelligent
role model growing up,
(Amy:)and now you can
be one for your nephew.
(Sheldon:)All right, I'll go.
(Sheldon:)But from what I've seen,
his attention span
(Sheldon:)is as limited as his bladder control.
(Bernadette:)You actually got him to do it.
(Rajj:)Yeah, you keep saying how much
Sheldon has affected all of us,
(Rajj:)but you've clearly
had an impact on him.
(Amy:)If that were true,
I wouldn't still be living alone.
(Amy:)Well, not exactly alone.
(Amy:)I do have a 50 pound sack of rice
(Amy:)with one of Sheldon's T-shirts on it.
(Leonard:)I'm telling you, Sheldon cares
for you more than you think.
(Amy:)I wish I could believe you.
(Amy:)I also wish there wasn't a mouse
living in Rice Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Hang on, I'm gonna give you a little
early Christmas present.